<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalProject_App</string>
    <string name="title_home">Select Attractions</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Schedule</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Profile</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!--  ATTRACTIONS DATA FOR RECYCLER VIEW-->
    <string-array name="attractions_name">

        <item>Roller Coaster</item>
        <item>Ferris Wheel</item>
        <item>Pirate ship</item>
        <item>Bumper cars</item>
        <item>Water slide</item>
        <item>Top spin</item>
        <item>The king</item>
        <item>Carousel</item>
        <item>Swings ride</item>
        <item>black mamba</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="attractions_description">
        <item>If you do not have the courage, do not try to get on this roller coaster at all!
                It will sweep you into a breathtaking gallop, accompanied by dizzying loops,
                sharp descents and twisting screws, almost unstoppable.
                Wait, wait: now make it all the way back by galloping backwards!
        </item>
        <item>
            An amusement facility that includes a standing wheel and passenger
            compartments that hang on its perimeter
        </item>
        <item>Only 5 daring pirates can sit on each bench. The journey is not simple
                the ship will move in a semicircle dozens of times, back and forth.
                A fun, experiential and exciting facility.
        </item>
        <item>New cars of various types are waiting for you, but we do not need a drivers license!
                You can accelerate, turn around and collide as you wish
        </item>
        <item>The four slides will take you downstream for an exciting experience that you
                will want to return to again and again. The slides are red for the little ones,
                the blue ones for the bigger ones.
        </item>
        <item>For the brave only! From the moment you sit down and fasten your seat belts,
                everything will happen at an insane speed: turn over, get stuck in the air with
                your head down and your feet up, turn 360 degrees and more .
        </item>
        <item>The king of extreme facilities, for the brave among you
                360 degree inversion operation, rises to a height of 25 meters and allows
                you to almost touch the clouds!
        </item>
        <item>A carousel is a type of amusement ride consisting of a rotating circular
                platform with seats for riders. The "seats" are traditionally in the form of
                rows of wooden horses or other animals mounted on posts
        </item>
        <item>The swing ride  is an amusement ride that is a variation on the carousel
                in which the seats are suspended from the rotating top of the carousel.
        </item>
        <item>An elevator that rises to a height of 65 meters and has 16 seats.
                On each trip, the sixteen passengers will ascend at high speed to the
                end and from there a rapid descent down and back for goodness sake.
        </item>



    </string-array>



    <integer-array name="attractions_age">
        <item>18</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>18</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>12</item>
    </integer-array>


    <integer-array name="attractions_height">
        <item>130</item>
        <item>130</item>
        <item>120</item>
        <item>95</item>
        <item>95</item>
        <item>140</item>
        <item>140</item>
        <item>95</item>
        <item>120</item>
        <item>130</item>
    </integer-array>


    <integer-array name="attractions_round">
        <item>2</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>1</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>